madewithstudio.com 2015-03-17

# Studio / Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY

  1. **Privacy** **.**  Use of the Application and the Services allow us to gather information from and about you. This section explains how we treat “ ** _Personal Information_** ” (information about you that is personally identifiable, like your name, address, email address, phone number and age, that may or may not otherwise be publicly available) that we collect when you (i) use the Application; (ii) complete the account registration process via the Application; or (iii) use the Services we offer. 
    1. General. We collect anonymous and Personal Information about you to provide you the most relevant information, products, programs and services that you request; to constantly improve the features, offerings and content that we provide through the Application; to personalize the content and advertisements provided to you; to determine how you use and respond to the features, offerings and advertisements on the Application; and to help offer you other products, programs or services that may interest you.
    2. Sharing with Third Parties. We do not share or distribute any of your Personal Information with Third Parties, except those required to provide the Services, such as with our merchant partner to process your monthly payment, our hosting partner which stores your information, and the like.
    3. Anonymous Information. Even if you do not provide us with any of your Personal Information, we may automatically track and collect other information when you use our Application, including without limitation the information that is made available to us through iOS. We aggregate such information to help us compile reports as to trends and other behavior about users visiting and using the Application; however such information is anonymous and cannot be tied directly to you.
    4. Cookies. We may also use “cookies” and your Personal Information to enhance your experience on the Application and to provide you with personalized offers. A cookie is a small data file placed on your device’s hard drive that contains information that allows us to track your activity on the Application. The cookie itself does not contain any Personal Information; however, if you provide any Personal Information to us, the cookie may act as an identifier to tie your Personal Information to your IP address or device. You may choose to delete cookies from your device’s hard drive at any time or to disable cookies on your device. If you delete cookies that relate to the Application, we may not be able to identify you upon your return to the Application. Additionally, if you disable your device’s cookies, you may not be able to access certain features of the Application that require that cookies be enabled. The cookies cannot be used to read data from your hard drive and cannot retrieve information from any other cookies created by other websites. Additionally, our cookies cannot be used as a virus, Trojan horse, worm or any other malicious tool that could impair your use of your device. Our cookies are used to help us better understand how you and other users use the Application so we can continue to provide a better, more personalized user experience on the Application.
